Cameron HOCHBERG

Game Developer

Recent French graduate in Computer Science from a US institution with a passion for game development. I have created multiple games using the Unity Engine. Also created the framework for 3D experiences in Unity and converted them to a 2D environment using Paper JS.

+1 (917)916-5247 +33 (0)6 21 20 58 76 French

cam.hochberg@gmail.com



<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Website</u> <u>Portfolio</u>

KEY SKILLS

Unity, C#, C++, Unreal Engine

EDUCATION

Bachelor & Master of Computer Science — Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio (United States)

From 2017 to May 2022

- · Focus on Networking and Security
- · Major Subjects: Advanced Game Design, Computer Security, Internet Security & Privacy, Machine Learning

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant — Case Western Reserve University Computer and Data Science department, Cleveland OH

From January 2021 to December 2021

- · Helping students (Undergrad and Graduate) with their homework and video game projects
- Creation of material for review sessions organized by teaching assistants each week

Al Research Assistant — Case Western Reserve University Computer and Data Science department Soumya Ray's research lab, Cleveland OH

From September 2019 to December 2020

- Helped to create an environment to test the efficiency of AI assistants using Unity, OpenHaptics Plugin
- Created the Passive and Active AI assistants used during testing Conversion of the experience from 3D to 2D

Full stack application analyst developer — SFEIR, Neuilly-Sur-Seine

From June 2020 to August 2020

- Created a memo on data protection and GDPR compliance
- Used SciPy to create a model to anonymize user input based on GDPR

Pen Test Intern — Armature Technologie, Paris

From May 2018 to July 2018

- Created a web app for pen testing report generation using Django
- · Organized the reports database
- · Created an associated API for easier access to this database

LANGUAGES

French Mother Tongue

English Bilingual (TOEFL 116/120)

Japanese Fluent (JLPT 3)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

<u>Programming Languages</u> C, Python, Rust, SQL, Java, PHP, HTML, Javascript, NodeJS

Technologies git, Godot, Docker, Unix,

Django, Sockets, TCP/UDP

DEVELOPED GAMES

- Butter'Em Up
- Wren and the Enchanted Forrest
- World Domination

HACKING COMPETITIONS

- BambooFox CTF 2021: 36/513
- Union CTF 2021: 53/466
- Google CTF 2021: 62/379 (Best Writeup prize for Pythia)
- ALLES! CTF 2021: 24/523
- Tokyo Westerners CTF 6th 2020: 59/648
- ALLES! CTF 2020: 48/470
- Google CTF 2020 : 161/625 (Best Writeup prize for Chunk Norris)